Shift change Happy Diwali
Be careful Don't be unaware of safety The
platoon of fire fighters makes this much
request Pay a little attention to safety Happy
Diwali Shaw
Don't wear loose clothes Wear cotton make-up
Keep a night water box nearby For
[praise]
Safety is useful in case of an accident Happy Diwali Be
careful Don't burst crackers in a closed place Jamma Hey, don't
burst,
jamma Keep all the windows closed Don't let an uninvited guest enter suddenly
Happy Diwali Be
careful If there is a fire somewhere, call us
immediately This is the number
10 The platoon of fire fighters makes this much
request Pay a little attention to safety
Happy Diwali Be
careful Like every year, some brave officers
will keep their promise of your safety So this Diwali do the difficult Be
careful and
keep your promise of celebrating Diwali responsibly
ICICI Labad keeps its promises